<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DataForce Technologies</title><link>https://dataforcetech.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on DataForce Technologies</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dataforcetech.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://dataforcetech.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dataforcetech.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;div class="about"&gt;
 &lt;img src="https://dataforcetech.github.io/images/dft-logo-transparent.png" alt="avatar" style="width:50%; height:auto;"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At DataForce Technologies (est. 2018), we specialize in helping organizations unlock the full potential of their data platforms. With over two decades of hands-on experience in database engineering, cloud migrations, and enterprise-scale performance optimization, we bring deep technical knowledge paired with a practical, business-focused approach. From Fortune 500 companies to fast-growing startups, our work ensures secure, scalable, and reliable data systems that enable smarter decisions and better outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our expertise spans SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL, and MongoDB Atlas, deployed across AWS, Azure, and hybrid environments. We focus on building automation frameworks, strengthening compliance and security, and optimizing performance—empowering engineering teams to deliver faster with confidence. Whether it’s migrating thousands of databases to the cloud, designing resilient high-availability solutions, or establishing CI/CD pipelines that reduce operational friction, we partner with you to simplify complexity and drive lasting results.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title/><link>https://dataforcetech.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dataforcetech.github.io/contact/</guid><description>&lt;div class="about"&gt;
 &lt;img src="https://dataforcetech.github.io/images/dft-logo-transparent.png" alt="avatar" style="width:50%; height:auto;"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have questions and might be interested in our services, I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to have a friendly, no-pressure conversation with you! With over 25 years of experience as a database professional, I bring a wide range of expertise across many database-related areas. And if your question happens to fall outside my wheelhouse, I’ll likely know where to point you for the right guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For inquiries please contact us via email at &lt;a href="mailto:dataforceusa@gmail.com" &gt;dataforceusa@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; &amp;#x1f4e7;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Códigos curtos</title><link>https://dataforcetech.github.io/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:51:36 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dataforcetech.github.io/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://dataforcetech.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dataforcetech.github.io/projects/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>